

ABOUT

Hey there. I'm a web developer and designer. I recently moved up to Portland, Oregon, which is the fourth city in the past five years where my wife, our adventure cats, and I have lived. Besides designing and coding websites, I enjoy hiking, reading books about philosophy, and drinking a good cup of coffee or tea.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF TOLEDO

B.B.A. Information Systems 2008 - 2012

CONTACT



jacobrokaw.com



@jacobrokaw



@jacobrokaw



jakebrokaw



jacobrokaw@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Q WEB DEVELOPER & DESIGNER

Formstack · Feb. 2015 - Present

I work remotely on the marketing design team. Some of my duties include: designing & building responsive web pages, optimizing our SEO, scaling our site's code, and designing marketing materials (i.e. PPC pages and graphics, icons, etc.). I am also the point person for our brand design system that we created and implemented for our marketing site.

DEVELOPER, IT APPLICATIONS

Nationwide Insurance • Feb. 2013 - Feb. 2015

I was the sole front-end developer on a team that handled one of Nationwide Insurance's financial applications. I also helped out other teams when they were updating their apps & sites to be fully responsive.

WEB SYSTEMS ASSOCIATE

Global Media Outreach · Jun. 2012 - Feb. 2013

I was one of six students to receive what started out as an internship out in San José, CA where I created and updated marketing sites and landing pages. As the internship ended, I was one of two students offered a part-time, remote position.

SKILLS & SOFTWARE

✓ Responsive Design

✓ HTML

✓ Design Systems

✓ CSS/SCSS

✓ A/B Testing

✓ JS/jQuery

✓ Atom/VS Code

✓ PHP

✓ Terminal/iTerm2

✓ Git/GitHub

✓ Sketch, Adobe CC

✓ InVision